Monday, June 8th
Good morning.
Good morning. Did you sleep all right?
Yeah. Thanks for the fresh bathwater.
Oh, sure.
The water was perfect. I appreciate it.
Sure.
But you don't have to do it again tonight.
Huh?
It's a waste of water.
Okay, I'm off to school.
Oh... Okay.
Yo, did you see that horror movie?
Yeah, I did!
Really?
The one everybody's talking about?
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Hey, I haven't seen it yet.
Oh, come on! You gotta go see it!
No way! Go see it already!
Episode 2 "A Deal and a Fried Egg"
I'm not really into horror movies, though.
Jeez, dude...
Give it up, man.
Maru.
Ayase, right? I know it's not cool to
interfere in someone else's love life,
but I'd advise against it.
It's not like that.
I'm not good enough for
a babe like her, anyway.
You got it backwards. If you went out
with Ayase, it'd make you look bad.
What do you mean?
Well, let's just say I've heard
some unpleasant rumors.
Rumors?
That she's a working girl.
You know, selling herself.
Huh?!
She's got blonde hair, pierced ears,
and a nasty look on her face
that always keeps people away.
It sounds like she's a troublemaker
who doesn't really fit in with her class.
Some people even swear they've
seen her leaving the love hotel district.
It's not like you to believe
rumors so easily, Maru.
One of the guys in the
baseball club asked her out.
Want to know what she told him?
"I'm just as bad as the rumors say."
"I have no intention of dating anyone."
Maybe he was just mad
over being shot down?
I doubt it.
I keep hearing the same story
from guys in other clubs, too.
Each claim by itself is hearsay, but when
they start to pile up, it sounds true, huh?
Yeah, basically.
Pandora...
Anyway, how's it going?
Huh?
You've got a new little sister now, right, bro?
Ah... yeah.
Crap. Gotta go change.
Huh? Oh, right.
Okay, here I go!
My secret weapon, the Great Celestial Serve!
Take... that!
Whoa!
Double fault.
Hey, where were you aiming, Maaya?
Sorry 'bout that!
Jeez. Why'd you have to hit it so hard?
Because it looks cooler that way! Tee-hee!
"Tee-hee," my butt, you little punk!
Hey! Wait, wait!
Now I gotcha!
I'm anti-violence!
Oh, yeah? Time for tickle torture!
I give, I give!
Please forgive me!
You skipping?
I regret my actions!
You scared me. Why are you talking to me here?
Do it right this time, okay?
But I am! I have been from the start!
When someone I know is skipping, I get worried.
No, you aren't!
All right!
So the big brother wants to
lecture his little sister, huh?
Okay, come on!
There!
I'm not in any position
to be lecturing anyone.
But I didn't know you'd picked tennis, too.
Aw, come on! Where are you hitting it? Jeez.
Maaya said we should pick the same sport.
One more time!
Of course, that wasn't my only reason.
Okay.
Here it comes!
You mean Narasaka-san, right?
You two are friends?
Hey! Again with that? Jeez!
We are. Although I think Maaya's
pretty much friends with everyone.
You might be right.
Why did you pick tennis, Asamura-kun?
It wasn't a very admirable reason.
I don't mind. My other reason
is pretty pathetic, too.
Because there aren't any team matches.
I don't like depending on anyone
or anyone depending on me.
Huh. We really do think alike.
How about you?
I didn't want to play a team
sport in the first place.
I usually try to keep my
distance from everyone.
Do you, maybe... have trouble
fitting in with your class?
You surprised?
Well, I always imagined that stylish girls
like you would be the center of attention.
I don't really mind it, though.
If people leave me alone,
that just gives me more time to myself.
Like time to listen to music?
Huh?
Oh.
Yeah, I guess.
Oh, Yuta-kun!
Ah, I just got back.
Welcome home. I made dinner for you.
Thank you very much.
Sorry to make you do all that before work.
What are you talking about?
You don't need to worry about that.
But dealing with customers
must be exhausting...
Well, I do deal with customers,
but I'm actually the bartender.
Oh, is that right?
I'd better get going. Let's talk about
dinner arrangements another time.
Ah, all right.
Please keep an eye on Saki for me.
Sure.
Well, I'm off.
See you later.
Welcome home.
You can come in.
I'm home.
Huh?
Oh, right. Welcome back.
Oh, were you studying?
This is bad for your eyes.
Thanks.
You're able to juggle work and school?
Is that really so strange?
Listen...
Do you know any easy part-time
jobs that pay really well?
I need more money, but I don't
want to waste a lot of time.
Maybe like an hour or two of
work for 10,000 yen or more.
Think that's doable?
Uh, well, I don't think you'll find
any normal jobs like that.
Really? I guess I gotta keep selling, then.
Selling?!
I read in a book that if you want to make
good money, you should sell yourself.
This might be really rude to say, but...
I don't mind. Go ahead.
I'm the one who asked, anyway.
I think you should take
better care of your body.
I already take good care of myself.
That's exactly why I want
to earn lots of money.
Would you be able to say
that in front of your mom?
Sure.
It'd probably make her happy.
She'd be like, "You've really grown up!"
What a way to raise your kid...
It wasn't like that for you?
Wasn't your father thrilled
when you first got into it?
If he was, that'd be a huge problem.
But wait, why are you talking
like I'm doing it, too?
Didn't you say something
about a job yesterday?
Huh?
I'm so sorry! I really am!
Don't worry about it.
Your food's getting cold.
I'm not surprised you
were confused about that.
I know what people think.
I know they wonder why I dress like this.
It's my armed mode.
Huh?
For me, these clothes are the armaments
that help me survive in society.
Oh...
So do they raise your defense stats?
Or let you dual attack or something?
You're pretty funny.
Am I?
I mean, I guess that's more or less right.
We face battles all the time.
Even if you don't see it.
Did you see my mom today?
Yeah.
Doesn't she look pretty when she goes to work?
Well... yeah. She sure does.
Saki and Yuta-kun,
Heat this up and eat it together, okay?
You know, she only graduated high school.
Oh, really?
Doesn't that bother you?
No, not really.
Huh. You sure are level-headed, Asamura-kun.
I've heard plenty from people
who aren't so neutral.
A beautiful woman with a high school
education who works in nightlife...
People say she's just stupid and
weaponizes her looks for everything.
I've heard people say that
about my mom so many times.
That's nonsense.
Right? It really is.
Yeah.
And it's so dirty when people try to
use that kind of logic to corner you.
How do you mean?
If you're smart but not pretty,
they label you a snobby, overeducated woman.
If you have good looks but aren't smart,
they say you're a gold digger
who's using her body to get ahead.
If a pretty woman relies on a man,
they say she's a parasite who has it easy.
But if she works hard for herself, they call
her a pathetic loser with no man to rely on.
I see what you mean.
So anyway, that's why I arm
myself with these clothes.
I need my look to be perfect
to make me stand out
before I have the strength to be
perfect at school and work, too.
This is the first step.
Are you okay with that?
It sounds utterly exhausting.
Even if it takes tons of energy, as long
as I can prove them wrong, it's worth it.
Prove them wrong, huh?
But who?
Aren't you like me, too?
I'm not as strong as you are.
But deep down,
you don't want anyone relying on you
or to rely on anyone else, right?
If you want to free yourself
of those expectations,
you need to be strong enough
to get by in life alone.
Is that why you're looking for a job?
So you can live independently,
without relying on anyone else?
Correct.
I'm sorry.
That was good.
I'll see if I can get you
some info about jobs.
Huh?
My senpai at work might have some ideas.
I'll ask her tomorrow.
Thanks.
But I don't want to make you
do everything for me.
It's all right.
No, it isn't. At least not to me.
Okay, how about miso soup?
Huh?
I want you to make me miso soup every day.
Is that your idea of a love confession?
Uh, no. That's not what I meant.
But today was the first time in years
I had miso soup that wasn't instant.
It was really delicious.
But I know Akiko-san has to work,
so that'd be asking a lot of her...
Fine by me.
I don't really mind cooking.
I'll look for job leads to help you
become independent, Ayase-san.
Okay. And I'll cook for you, Asamura-kun.
Tuesday, June 9th
Yuta, you won't believe this!
What's wrong? You're gonna wake Akiko-san up.
But S-Saki-chan is...
Oh, good morning.
Why are you making breakfast?
Why? We made a deal yesterday.
Yeah, but that was about dinner.
I figured I might as well make breakfast, too.
It's my personal policy
to give more than I take.
I see.
Asamura
Ayase
Saki-chan, thanks for breakfast!
It was delicious! I'm so impressed!
I'm off now!
You don't like it?
Uh, no, it's not that.
You can be honest with me.
No, really. I'm just used to eating
fried eggs with soy sauce.
Oh, really?
We've always used salt and pepper. Sorry.
It's fine! You had no way of knowing.
It's my fault for not telling you.
From now on, I'll try to ask ahead of time.
Okay. I'll try to keep you informed
about stuff, too.
Okay.
I had no idea you were so into
self-improvement, my sweet junior!
Super Moneymaking
Huh? Oh.
No, this is something else. How do I explain?
Hmm?
I want to live on my own
after graduating high school,
so I need to save up for that.
Oh, no wonder.
Now that I have a little sister at my age,
living at home might get a little cramped.
Especially since we're the same age.
I can understand wanting to live on your own,
but it isn't actually
because of your sister, right?
It isn't?
Well, I guess it could be,
but it just seems like a waste.
Having a sister your age
could be a great asset!
If you can't get by on your own, I think
it's perfectly fine to rely on someone else.
Even if I become a burden on them?
You know, some people actually
prefer women who are a burden.
Well, that's just personal preference.
It definitely is.
But listen, that's what money is all about.
Super Moneymaking
Earn More the Smart Way
Investment Tips You Should Know
It's nice if you have it,
but if not, that's fine, too.
Just find someone to take care of you.
Is that all there is to it?
Even rich CEOs are more dependent on
other people than you might imagine, son.
Don't talk like you know. It's not a good look.
You don't think a charming college girl like
myself would have a sugar daddy or two?
Just kidding!
You dumbass.
Well, anyway, why don't you rethink
depending on your family a little more?
The right way to depend on people?
Sorry.
I'm still looking for leads on jobs,
but I thought this might be useful, too.
I didn't know you had any
close female friends.
That's what you got from this?
I'm rooting for you.
For what?
She sounds like the lovely, friendly,
very intelligent older sister type.
Eh...
I think what she said is true.
Yeah.
But I still want to become self-reliant.
You don't feel like you can
depend on me and my dad?
No, I know you're wonderful people.
I think you're both very dependable.
But...
this whole thing might have been easier
if you were terrible people instead.
Huh?
Sorry. Thanks for the food.
Wednesday, June 10th
Aw, Maaya, that's way too high!
Tee-hee!
"Tee-hee," my butt!
If you do that again, I'm gonna get mad.
Here.
Thanks!
I think I'm starting to get the hang of it...
You can't do that.
I mean it.
You think I can just let it go when you
do things that could get you killed?
Sorry.
I wonder if it's gonna start soon.
It looks fine, though.
Sniff, sniff, sniff, sniff, sniff!
See, this is what it smells
like before it rains!
That's kind of weird.
Two hundred percent accurate!
I'm home.
Or whatever.
We face battles all the time.
Even if you don't see it.
As long as I can prove
them wrong, it's worth it.
One New Message
Episode 3 "Reflection and Revision"